export const QUESTIONS_DATA = [
    {
        "question": "The capital of Indonesia",
        "choices" : [ 
            "Jakarta",
            "Singapore",
            "Kuala Lumpur",
            "Seoul",
        ],
        "answer" : "Jakarta",
    },
    {
        "question": "Kuala Lumpur is the Capital of",
        "choices" : [
            "Indonesia",
            "Singapore",
            "Malaysia",
            "Korea",
        ],
        "answer" : "Malaysia",
    },
    {
        "question": "Australia is part of Asia",
        "choices" : [
            "True",
            "False",
        ],
        "answer" : "False",
    },
    {
        "question": "Number of continents",
        "choices" : [
            "1",
            "10",
            "5",
            "7",
        ],
        "answer" : "5",
    },
    {
        "question": "Is a timezone",
        "choices" : [
            "UTC",
            "UTF",
            "WIB",
            "HTML",
        ],
        "answer" : "UTC",
    },
    {
        "question": "Number of countries in ASEAN",
        "choices" : [
            "5",
            "10",
            "2",
            "15",
        ],
        "answer" : "5",
    },
    {
        "question": "Largest country in the world",
        "choices" : [
            "Indonesia",
            "China",
            "Russia",
            "Japan",
        ],
        "answer" : "Indonesia",
    },
    {
        "question": "Currency used in America",
        "choices" : [
           "USD",
           "JPY",
           "SGD",
           "IDR",
        ],
        "answer" : "USD",
    },
    {
        "question": "Bali is in",
        "choices" : [
            "Japan",
            "Indonesia",
            "America",
            "Australia",
        ],
        "answer" : "Indonesia",
    },
    {
        "question": "Indonesia is a tropical country",
        "choices" : [
            "True",
            "False",
        ],
        "answer" : "True",
    },
]